<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hillffair</string>
    <string name="main">Home Page</string>
    <string name="user_name">ABCDEF</string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="gotit">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="screen1_head">Hillffair 2k16</string>
    <string name="screen2_head">Enjoy</string>
    <string name="screen3_head">Party</string>
    <string name="screen4_head">Fun</string>

    <string name="screen1_body">Cultural fest oh nith 2016</string>
    <string name="screen2_body">Thousands of events</string>
    <string name="screen3_body">abcd efgh ijhl mnop qrst</string>
    <string name="screen4_body">great great great</string>


    <string name="signup"> Already have an account <a href=""><b>Log In</b></a></string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">homeActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>


    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password </string>
    <string name="registration_button">Register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">Contacts permissions are needed for providing email completions.</string>
    <string name="no_text"> </string>
    <string name="registration_message">You are not registered yet. Use the registration button to complete your registration.</string>
    <string name="registration_failed">Your email or password is already in use</string>
    <string name="quiz_comment">*Make sure to read all instructions before Attempting Quiz</string>
    <string name="sample_question">Number of original members in Justice league?</string>
    <string name="quiz_instruction">Please read below instruction very carefully:-\n\n
    1. This quiz is hosted by Appteam of NIT Hamirpur.\n\n
    2. <b>Important:</b> Make sure that your device remains connected to Internet while attempting quiz.\n\n
    3. Make sure that all personal information about you in current account is correct, otherwise you may be disqualified.\n\n
    4. When you enter the quiz, you will be provided with a set of 10 randomly chosen questions.\n\n
    5. Each question is unique and will not appear again. \n\n
    6. Their is no negative marking for wrong answer, so it is better to attempt all questions. And for correct answer you will be provided one point.\n\n
    7. <b>Important:</b> Time limit to attempt a set of question is 2 minutes. \nYou have to finish the quiz in 2 minutes to make your score count.\n\n
    8. After attempting all questions press finish button to submit your inputs. After 2 minutes, inputs will automatically gets submitted.\n\n
    9. <b>Important:</b> Make sure u are connected to internet wile attempting quiz, and while making submission.\n\n
    10. Do not close app after starting quiz, because you will be given only one attempt to each set of questions.\n\n
    11. After clicking on submit you will be shown only score corresponding to that set of questions.\n\n
    12. <b>Advice:</b> Attempt as many sets possible to score more points.\n\n
    13. Winners will be announced after Hillffair 2016, and will be rewarded.\n\n
    14. For any queries/complaints/bugs, contact us at appteam.nith@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="open_source_licenses">Licenses</string>
    <string name="licenses_text">
    This project is currently licensed under the GNU General Public License v3.\n\n
        \t<a href="https://github.com/bumptech/glide">Glide</a>\n\n
\t<a href="https://square.github.io/retrofit/#license">Android Retrofit Library</a>\n\n
\t<a href="https://github.com/code-mc/loadtoast">Load Toast</a>\n\n
    </string>
    <string-array name="autocomplete">
        <item>johnpaul@yahoo.com</item>
        <item>marykate@yahoo.com</item>
        <item>kelvinjames@yahoo.com</item>
        <item>henrysweart@gmail.com</item>
        <item>gracepowell@yahoo.com</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_about_hillffair">aboutHillffairActivity</string>
    <string name="about_hillffair">

It is a name which needs no introduction up here in the hills, it is the reason why most of northern India awaits the month of November,
it is the name whose mention alone excites the listener to his core. \n\nHill’ffair is around the corner once again. And needless to say,
it promises to be more extravagant this year than ever before. \n\nIn the age where fests are in a perennial quest to provide all who bear witness an unforgettable and worth
cherishing experience, Hill’ffair has become synonymous with exhilarating joy and excitement that knows no bounds.
\n\nWith its unique theme, “ComiCon” this year, Hill’ffair 2016 promises a journey into the world of fantasy, where imagination knows no bounds and where the intellect gains
its ultimate ecstasy. \n\nA journey through the animated joys of the world, which is destined to leave you spell bounded, a chance to watch those fantasies come alive and to
relish the unreal.\n\n
So now you know where you have to be this November!!!\n\nNIT Hamirpur and its hospitality awaits you. Come watch the magic unfold at NIT Hamirpur.
</string>
    <string name="aboutus_text">A Open Source Project by <a href="https://github.com/appteam-nith/">AppTeam NITH</a> for Cultural Festival Hillffair 2k16.\n\nSource code available at
        <a href="https://github.com/appteam-nith/Hillffair">GitHub</a> \n\nLink : \nhttps://github.com/appteam-nith/Hillffair\n
    </string>
</resources>
